[ Pause ]
>> Master, reinforce and divide.
All you who believe fasting is decreed for you as opposed to
breathing for loss before you let you make a sense and best.
So fasting was decreed before.
It was originally the Putno.
It was like all religious practices in his life.
Besting was decreed through Abraham.
The injunction to him it reinforced throughout the month of fasting.
The divine is here to allow him to force during the night of fasting.
So when fasting was
decreed first to Abraham,
There is no intercourse.
There is throughout the whole month.
The Ramadan.
At the heart of the festival, it's a festival for food, drink and sex.
Throughout the Ramadan.
As you will see here in the next lecture,
actually it's in verse 187.
You will see that this will modify to allow interforce during the minds of Ramadan.
of Ramadan.
When 84, you shall fast during the specified days.
Specified days means the last month of the UNA period.
Just a month of Ramadan, the month of Ramadan existed before Muhammad was born.
You should fast during the specified days.
The specified days are identified by the appearance of the new move,
or the ninth month, and end by the appearance of the new move of the tenth month.
Those who are in or traveled may be fast and equal number of other days.
and also find it too difficult to substitute the fee of a poor person for each day or faster.
You see, God, there are levels of all kinds of outlets.
Whatever the reasons, if it cannot fast, there is almost an altitude.
You can feed a poor person for every day.
If you're here, or traveling, there's hardship, and you can pause the problem that has to be.
All these other associations,
analysis from that.
Those who find it too difficult may substitute the healing of a poor person
for each day of fasting.
If very volunteers to feed more people, it would be better to make that.
And that, not just the end of the church,
but fasting is the best for you, if you own the new.
So after all these analysis, whatever excuses, the reasons, even though God gives you permission to break your fasting,
it is fasting is best for you. So if you can, but anyway, fast, then go ahead, it is best for you to fast.
Nobody dies from our stance and from what we want to do for one day.
24 hours, because 24 hours is only an excellent 16 hours.
Nobody was done of lack of food and water.
So it is best for us to do cutting out of this commitment for the best.
What is it for?
Ramadan is the month during which the Quran was revealed.
This is a very important step because the legend and stories
and so forth continue the Quran was revealed over a period of 23 years.
Obviously it is not true.
But this verse is says Ramadan is the month during which the Quran was revealed.
The fact is throughout the Qur'an, we spoke that the Prophet Muhammad was taken on the
night of power the 37th night of Ramadan, of that year, that first day, he was taken
after the highest horizon in the Qur'an.
And the Qur'an was putting his heart, the whole Qur'an, from that one night.
like you and I have in our heart the knowledge that God is the local community.
That we bore witness that God is our Lord.
But we don't remember that because it's inside our heart.
We don't perceive it as an hour instead.
And in the same way that the Lord was put in the hand of its heart.
So, 53 gives the details. Now, he was taken to the highest horizon, and the old ground
was put in his heart. Subsequent to this, Gavin will go and bring out a portion of the
for a portion that is small enough for the profit and his companions to memorize.
For finance, the SAW 17 says we release the good art in small portions in order to make
memorize. Now all these references are shown at the very beginning of the book,
the beginning of the first few pages, there's one of the big words on page that says, "On
the 27th night of Ramadan, you see that page?
On the 27th night of Ramadan of the year, 13 before Israel, with the 610 AD, the Prophet
Muhammad was summoned to the highest possible point and messaged the nahsa.
the opposite of the other side as the highest possible form.
And this parabola plays into this car.
As we see in 297, 17, 1, 4, 3, 53, 1, 2, 3,
and 97, 1, 2, 5.
Subsequently, the parabola was released
through a mahatmaic mouth over a period of 23 years,
namely between 6th and 632 AD.
At the moment of release, it was copulously written down and divinely guarded since then.
Now this is not for the majority of Muslims around the world to believe.
Okay. They have stories that can come at ease from other sources, storytellers.
He said, "I don't know how to read and so forth." So he said, "The story tells you that the gratias something that gratias is respected to a massive loxel going up to the seventh day." So at the time, of course, the results of the spring has massive loxel. But most people don't think it would have.
Must have lost and Jerusalem was whipped after the fact. 70 years after the fact.
And then the story tellers made up the story of Tim
That wasn't the first day of revelation.
It was supposed to be the very seventh,
one hundred years,
according to the message.
So, what are we looking for,
and they put all these steps together
and you reach the truth.
I wanted to look at 2 of 44,
verse 3, for example.
What it's called to be.
Step forward, the subject is very clear.
It's amazing how the average Muslim one really is different
than the soft one, the truth of the parabh.
Another common congruent.
We see the mark, if you look at the mark,
24 to the center.
3.
3, 24, 14, 14.
There are 44.
That's 3, it says 1.
And now, we're going to do the rest of the day,
We have revealed the Torah in a blessed night. So the Torah was revealed in one night. So the Palano was revealed in one night.
the first thing that was released was the solar microsics, the first five verses. The
The release of our country is on the section of the time.
The rear look on and the rear look on.
A few verses.
This is what all the reviewers have come to.
The first thing that was released was the solar 96,
the first 5 verses, 19 words.
The second release was 38th World of '68.
The third release was 57th World of '74.
The fourth release was up to the number 19 of '75.
The fifth release was the first complete sword at best,
which means the 19th of Bismillahman and the main thing immediately after the number 19.
He received the Quran in his life.
He was taken up in the cemetery.
When he received the Quran in his life, he was taken up in the cemetery.
a little bit of the site up behind him.
So he didn't even know it.
He was scared out of the end of the debris
and then he'd come and he'd take it over and bring it out.
One of those was, he was weird and exotic
but it was so kind of even the couldn't have it.
He was different though, whether it was something happened.
Because,
Dr. Zusz, to show him our martyrs,
he was absolutely, he was completely aware of certain things,
that he was definitely aware of.
He was not imagining things he was seeing,
where he had to be.
So he was aware that he was being appointed as the final prophet,
But he was given the message.
But like some other verses, it tells the prophet not
to hurry with the declaration.
So what I'm saying is he aware that if he's there in him,
he wouldn't quite clear what he did.
Yes, I'm sure he can.
And then the case was who thought
that all the key was a way.
Because Gabriel was spending his life--
When Gavin can not just release the one you came in the whole budget instructions along
with the black for example, these verses blown in Surah 19 or Surah 16 in the specific
position and this is now a new Surah and the champion entitled Jonah.
So instructions.
Or as of now, we're very important for zero speed.
Or as of now, we can't do the whole situation.
How does it detail to be formed in these histories?
When the Army reports it in the for a lot?
No, I mean, the bad times that we have the objective.
Yes.
But there's a whole family now that's taken away.
Right, spin vector with the p instead of m,
which is the sense that the unknowns
in the divine orbit.
Because you can set in vector if you have a ball,
you have a balloon, and a balloon is blocked.
So vectoring is a vectoring.
So the profit may have, maybe every other floor or something.
The first sign, "bit" for the people is vectoring.
Hey, Gabriel, are you sure it is vectoring?
So we give here and it's much better.
So he would make his very views of this
to be written with a beat.
And as I was showing rather than Hamad to the other typical
written with an M, the whole system
of the whole movement, the movement
and the system of the left was-- it is really overwhelming.
But God picked out a word that is most
familiar to the Arab, to the front.
He went up to Muhammad.
He was born there because his town.
It is not Mecca, the people who go north and south.
They give that in, they know it is Mecca, so what makes it effective?
Also shows the absolute obedience to the revolution.
God has said this is the revolution we will be.
Somebody said, "You know, I want you to write down,
You know, when the divine authors came to write into the theme, that's it.
You don't know if he was not done to you. Is he talking with you?
And they stand like this, the generation that came after, they didn't take a correctly.
They know that it is Mecca, but they didn't there.
Of course, they must remember God guaranteed the preservation of Quran.
So, even if they tried, they perished. I'm sure some people like it.
It's very interesting because this not only shows that the spelling, it was not the normal one, has been preserved.
But later on people begin to notice that there's a difference.
Then they begin to say, "Oh, this is another name of."
But then there is no proof of that.
>> This peculiar, this is another name.
When the most possible explanation is that it was there from the beginning,
and nobody wanted to touch it.
They were afraid.
>> It's interesting how when people make up an interpretation,
they back it up with all parts of stories.
For example, I would I am alluding, said that the letters before the soldiers, for example,
were put at the beginning of the soldiers to gain the attention of the people, to say,
"Come, what will I imagine?"
So people would say, "What?"
And so they get their attention.
And he said that this was a common thing in the Arabic literature.
This is to back up his interpretation.
It's very simple.
All you need to do is show us some literature.
They have these letters. It's not true.
You're just connecting all upset because all the seconds are there.
Why do you make a statement like that?
It's very common ancient Arabic literature.
I studied ancient Arabic literature.
We haven't recorded it in a Python, like that, all these things.
And there isn't most of them.
These persons are not common at all.
But we will never use any circumstances.
- Well, if Marludy follows his own thinking,
he should put A.M. before his books.
You see, what's A.M.?
He should have rather a lot of movies.
- Get your attention.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
(mumbling)
- No, that is guessful, please.
- Why?
- He explained it on his son of a million attention.
- Exactly.
This is another point.
Why?
The netizens in front of only 29 chapters.
But that doesn't want us to pay attention to other chapters, what?
But they have people, the interpreters, and back up their interpretations of their stories
that can absolutely no basis.
So that means that the crime on the stand, you know, is what?
When one of the regulations came out, you know, there was always a matter to write it out.
Right.
Yeah.
And how do you know what how differentiates the two men was just something that we would
say, you know, natural technology, and the same level of information?
How do you get them to, because, uh, Muhammad couldn't miss the visit of the Gabbie,
the Gabbie visits you, and they had missed that.
No, his question I think is this.
His question is this that, how did the people around him, when the Prophet was reciting,
when the Prophet was reciting, how would the people around him know that now he is reciting
Quran, but at other times he is just talking from his own.
How did the people know?
My answer was I can't miss Gabriel's visit.
So what Gabriel says and says comes and says,
"Who will I have a mom who's someone who's ready for the new
network level for the ride?"
And filling this with the ground, the newest,
the nearest there with a hundred, a hundred,
no more reasons here.
And then we say to the liberation
I have some more ground now.
You see what is it?
You said, "Well, I had a loan, someone."
And they write it down and then they sit and stop it and memorize it.
Just like we're doing now.
That's what's wrong.
But that actually is a very cool country, this is certainly one of the wonderful things.
It's the sera con abi, the history of the Bible, the perfect.
It's to be big.
The people around him knew, they knew very well when he was under inspiration.
And then they themselves would hear what he's saying and they would memorize it.
The people around him.
They were actually with him.
They knew.
The people knew the difference.
It is a very, very beautiful thing.
They also know when he would just speak, you know, or the other thing.
Although I don't know how to do it, he is not enough, he changes.
Because in some ways it's a form of, he becomes an instrument.
They know from his face and his utterance.
It's not his, it's not his language.
It's just like, for example, all of us now, we know how the way it goes to us.
But imagine if you're talking like Shakespeare, we all know that it's not you.
It's a very wonderful phenomenon how the people with teeth would know that he's a
regulation and they would themselves memorize it when he is at the...
As far as the physical changes are concerned, I really don't buy them.
They used to spend some time wearing something.
Obviously, there are some doctors like those that are interested.
I really need something wrong.
I really don't buy them.
But I don't go that far.
I always say that there are some things they know, but that is a pleasure to be called.
But it does suffer from the gist of the box.
You can say that people will pay for these uncleses or these things.
According to a doctor, a Jesuit doctor in Philippines, an American doctor, he is saying,
and he does not believe in the Quran.
He is even an enemy of Islam.
But these men taught us very clearly from the medical point of view, these recitations
not have come from an epileptic disease.
Yes, well, that's a epileptic story.
I don't blame them because they make up these stories.
But if you look at 17106--
[INAUDIBLE]
Chapter?
17.
[INAUDIBLE]
This is page 196 of the top.
It says, "This is the Quran that we
decree to be released to the people by you over a long period,
though we sent it down all at once.
That's not the one that they want.
This is Daniel Hood.
That's a good one, but there is one.
[indistinct chatter]
But there is one test to fix it in memory.
I'm going to find it to the important.
It says that we released it over a long period,
and ordered to fix it in memory.
This would indicate to me that the Gabbard would release a few verses
and then would settle behind that ability of memory.
Now, I want to remind you also of the edges that went to Abraham, visited him in the form
of human beings.
Did Abraham went and snotted the cap for them, roasted the cap and brought it to them?
The edges not deep, but they didn't have the same digestive system as Abraham.
The needs that we have, neither will you and the children of real life, you will not need
But anyway, the engines wouldn't eat the roasted can that Abraham had brought.
So this tells us that the engines come to the people in the form of human beings.
They come to Abraham and there's no reason why Abraham wouldn't come to the company
for the human being and help him release the bronze and they can memorize it.
Oh, here is the...
This is a very important versus we're talking about the revelation of the Quran.
25, 32, 25, so are 25, verse 3, 2.
Because you are the most important people in the world.
That's my strategy.
It's 10-2-4-7.
Verse 3-2 says, "The disbelieve or said, 'How come the parabu is not revealed through him all at once?'
We thus released it gradually in order to fix it through your memory.
That's the reason why it was released over a period of 23 years.
The
property memory and the companion support were around and they were also memorizing along
with him.
They didn't know how to read or write but that gave him a soft memory and gave him a lot
of time.
Nothing else to do.
It was really a text a lot of time to memorize it and to keep it alive with your memory.
So let's do fix it in your memory, indicates that the government will release it and do
versus and then with the next 100, no, memorize it.
So what are the areas of item for there or not?
When the Prophet met them, he would send somebody to bring them, he would tell them,
I have some new Quran to it.
And you write it down.
Yes, that is interesting.
Could it also,
would it not be reasonable to say,
that it makes sense why the Quran has to be among other reasons,
and referring only to some verses.
It makes sense why the Quran has to be revealed on different occasions,
because some of them are really guides for specific
for a specific occasion.
For example, after the battle of bad,
after the battle of old, how can manipulation
talk about the results of the battle of over thieves?
Before the text plays.
Yeah, if this is not a taken place.
So that's why if I'm allowed to use
a kind of philosophical language,
the de corral, as you say, is given as a rule,
in the heart of the Prophet and release at different times.
The releasing is there actually in the heart,
but potentially for certain occasions.
Every location comes, it becomes afterlife,
directly to the occasion.
That was the occasion of Zay and the border is white and now the Quran was written before the earth was created
and the most potent Muhammad's heart before these things took place
it's one of the miraculous pieces of Quran so when Zay, the force was white and the prophet was to marry Zay to white
then these verses were released and that was the time for it
so this is a very good point for Diitma Khul's history
Okay, back to.
(inaudible)
When we go to that, there is this.
Very interesting.
But it's very interesting because, you know,
there was this movie, because actually it was there,
but it was keeping it, if you want, you remember?
Yeah, I remember all the two mighty--
Yes, he was there.
It was there.
It was supposed to come out in a revelation, but he--
I think he scolded by the Quran.
Did you not point it out?
Oh, yeah.
This is a sort of something for him.
He's scolded.
This is a claim.
But there are many different kinds of inspiration
and the liberation.
There is a kind where you put in a situation
where you're not submit to God or you'll object.
So he was put in that kind of situation.
The situation where he was appeared
with the people in the people.
But when a certain inspiration comes to you,
And you just can't take advantage of yours.
Like Moses mother, for example, throwing her baby in the river.
And whoever heard of Linda's normal mysh and just in the river.
Any mother of the...
No mother of the world would do that, simply to be a Linda of her own.
But it's all some kind of an impulse.
See, we all know what the loving mother you are in this.
He uses an example for that.
See, what kind of mother's done?
She's probably beaten that.
Very soon, very soon.
But this is the kind of inspiration that's just text all over this.
There's nothing else you can do.
[ Inaudible ]
>> All of the direct government programs.
The government programs, but not once in too many,
like the white, to establish a law, a president.
That was the idea.
I mean, it could be in any form.
So under Puran, not it.
Okay, back to our 85.
Ramadan is the month during which the Puranos reveal.
And I think we really started this point, currently.
Breaking guidance, clear guideline, and the statute book.
Thank you for being the book of laws, regulations, the final law.
Initially the commander, you should not kill for example. That's it.
But the Brown gives details about the process of equivalence, the law of equivalence, and the hardening man for the man, the woman for the woman.
God wishes convenience for you rather than heart.
He wishes to enable you to fulfill your duty and to glorify God and guide in you and to
show your appreciation.
When you say, "I believe in God," you have to do something about it.
You can just say, "I believe in God."
Then you don't play the five players.
Or you don't pass the marker on the dot.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about that.
You were family.
What was family?
How did you say?
My idea is how did you say?
[ Inaudible ]
The answer is to become Jewish to compete one poor person. And then it ends with the best food fast. Even in the half long day, nobody would die from an absence of a good and great food system.
It's hard, it's not easy. This would show your appreciation of God, such a really believe in God. And what He says, you fast in the matter of the world, you fast in the matter of what.
And as you know, pregnancy, yes, it gets hard.
It's hard. You can do it some other time.
You can do it especially for you.
And for you, too, for God's sake, especially for you.
Look at that.
It's beautiful.
Oh, it's really nice.
Did you pass?
[ Inaudible ]
[ Laughter ]
I want to say that, you know, how the God designed the whole life of the test, we do
say that madam comes in the short days in the winter, where the days were only eight
hours and fasting is really not in this.
This was a few pre-
breakfast and lunch,
mostly, so there's nothing to it.
And let's take 100 people who would pass
when the day is short.
And then Ramadan moves,
and the day has become longer.
And 15 people will drop out when the day is 10 hours.
Now we'll have 85 people faster.
And then the day becomes 14 hours.
The first thing is that 20 more people drop out, so we have 65 people left.
And then the day goes on to 15 hours and 21 people drop out because it's too long.
Then you have 25 people left.
And then the day is 16 hours, half, the wrong and half, 16 hours, and you have.
to any more people, well, about 25%,
that these are the 25 die-hard believers
who will trust no matter what.
And you can see how the test is designed.
The whole universe is designed for that test.
The same with the prayer.
Now we are praying, for instance,
before sunrise, when we like it or not.
Because for some reason, it's still in theory.
You have to get work, otherwise, or whatever.
So you'll pray.
Now, are you praying, president, before sunrise,
because God says you pray before sunrise,
or because you have to go towards the day of the clock.
Now, the through you, this question
will be answered when sunrise is at work, right?
Gonna pray, president, before sunrise,
or gonna pray at seven o'clock this week.
That will show you whether you are praying for it because God said so and because your boss said come to work at every time.
The whole universe is designed for the test. The access of the earth is 50 to 23 degrees just so the days will be longer.
Just to test you.
You see the point?
When God says you prayed morning before sunrise, this means as a time heart believer, as one
who really believes in God, who knows that God is the most who runs your life and provides
for you and promises to make you, I think, or queen of earth.
You believe the Quran, you know all these things, then you will get up to pray first, even if the sunrise is full of you, whatever, doesn't matter.
And this is what this person needs by showing the appreciation of God.
Appreciation of God needs to appreciate that he needs the master, he needs the king, the fulfillment he says must go.
He doesn't want to bother you and disturb you and get you up and forth after the morning.
He doesn't need our prayer.
But he said, "This is what's good for you, this is for me."
This one prepares you to join my kingdom, to suggest that God says.
Because the day will come when you are resurrected to enter the eternal light, the real light.
And glottalize a few minutes and then open them, imagining that you're opening them on the day of resurrection.
Now what would your position be?
Are you qualified to join the kingdom of God?
Or were you lazy?
You couldn't get up before sunrise, oh God.
But when your boss says you come, you're going to have an emergency and you have to come
at three o'clock every morning for the next two weeks.
When you go, three o'clock every morning for two weeks.
But you want to get fired.
But that's what distinguishes the believer from the lazy person.
And don't be discouraged. If you understand where you're playing one player a day,
well, hopefully you will always progress. That's what counts.
This is the motto of general ethics, progress, or most important, because progress is our
most important thing is that you do not regress into not praying.
You must progress into doing two prayers a day, and from that you progress to doing
three prayers a day and so forth.
You make a point of never regret.
Maybe you will never pay money before so far.
At least I don't mean this Christ,
because your body is a white horse,
it's a time to train.
So yes, real white horse.
Your body is real white.
Doesn't want to get up in the morning.
It's very difficult to get up in the morning.
And this is the whole idea because if you're strong,
you will make your body get up.
If you're body is stronger than you're strong,
than you're deep trouble,
but trying to exercise your soul
until you're stronger than you're body
because your body's gonna die,
and you're gonna stay on.
You're gonna stay up as a strong person
as a week, week, baby.
So it's very important to do it.
Don't be discouraged.
And the next progress, we must enforce the progress.
Okay.
Progress from one prayer, a day to two prayers a day.
Until you do the five prayers a day,
and then you progress to praying,
praying, patter, every day.
Because God says to him.
So, God, he says, he wishes that you will fulfill your duties.
He wants you to fulfill your duties.
But the test requires that God does not interfere.
So, sentence of the angel will not cry out.
The idea is that God does not interfere, but God wants you to be saved.
God wants you to join this kingdom.
He wants you to be, I think, a queen on earth.
He wants you to have absolutely no masters.
Except here.
So that's what this verse is saying.
He wishes to enable you to put federal Jews.
He wants you to pass the test.
But people insist on climbing the tents into hell.
God puts tents in front of them to prevent them from going to hell for their insists.
God wishes to elaborate on the material duty and to fulfill it, to glorify God for guiding you,
and to show your appreciation by casting the month of Ramadan,
by praying the five prayers in their time,
by giving to charity, being charitable, kind.
This country is under a terrible test right now.
We've got the charges and the four people.
And you should hear all the mean, average Americans.
They come all unfather with help.
They were thinking in Phoenix or building a car for the charges.
and some refuse. And you should hear all the people speaking against this. We are
guilty of the city. It's like it's their choice to be poor or hungry or whatever.
But this is a test for this country. And I must be a scientist, must be kind, must be
not be thankful that he is not putting that position.
They are human beings.
They're having their own tests in the own way.
So these are the duties that God wants us to fulfill.
It's a lot of prayer, it's a catch-out, it's a festival from Adam.
God's feeling is what we can.
Now look at 186.
And what my servants ask you about me, I am always needed.
I respond to the call of any calling who calls on me.
Therefore you shall respond to me and believe in me that they may attend by me.
So these are the requirements that you pray are the answers.
Are you prayer's answers?
They should be always.
If you fulfill the requirements, respond to me, respond to God, and believe in God.
People who believe in God respond to Him, respond meaning they follow His commandments.
That means here's your cause, to bring your cause.
That says it's closer to you than the Zegelian Vane.
What do you listen to?
It's closer to you than this.
How could you close it?
Because God controls the count of blood cells in your veins.
It controls that, the blood in your veins.
What verse is that?
It is closer to you than your Zegelian Vane?
I think it's through an 86th of the...
(indistinct)
[ Inaudible ]
>> 50, 16.
>> Yeah.
>> So, 50 versus 16.
Since we created the human being, we are fully aware of his innermost thoughts to our closer
to happen in juggle of pain.
I was going to turn the heat up now.
No, is it up? Okay.
Can you hear me?
So what my servants ask you about me, I am always near.
Now, you may pray for something,
and because you are a good believer, you pray as answered,
But not exactly at the time you want it because
God is not
Sometimes we say don't say
around to put this but
As a king or queen on earth the engines are all around you and they're eager to
defend whatever you want
So sometimes you may make statements and they rush into fulfilling those statements on the
orong because they don't know your thoughts.
And you may get them from it this way.
But the guard is, when you pray to God he knows what is best for you, what is the best time.
So you may pray for something that is not good for you at this particular time.
And your prayer will come to pass after exact the best time for you, at the right time.
And if you recall, I give you an example of who I thought that the prayer takes three to six months to get from prison.
Remember that story?
[laughter]
You know, I was thinking of seven universities and how far it is, and I say, "Well..."
I noticed that was my conclusion, that when I pray for something, it is for prison, but it takes three or six months.
So I came to the final conclusion that it takes three to six months for God to answer the phrase.
And the day I came to that conclusion, I hit that I was driving down the street in Tripoli,
live here and I hit that kid in the head, in the head.
And I was going so fast it took me a half a block to stop.
That kid was laying down on the side of the street and was supposed to be there.
a